const db = require('../conection/conection')

const QuestionRes = [
    {
        question: "Qual seu nome?",
        response: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Qual sua idade?",
        response: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Onde voce mora",
        response: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "O que voce faz?",
        response: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "O que voce tem?",
        response: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "O que voce quer?",
        response: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Onde andas?",
        response: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Onde foi?",
        response: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Onde queres?",
        response: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "O que gostaria?",
        response: "a"
    }
]


